Sculpture Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Renaissance (Box 9)
  - 20th century (Box 9)
    - Fontana, Lucio, 1899-1968 (Box 11)
    - Francesco di Giorgio, 1439-1502 (Box 11)
    - Gagini, Domenico, 1448-1536 (Box 11)
    - Galletti, Stefano, 1833-1905 (Box 11)
    - Ghiberti, Lorenzo, 1378-1455 (Box 11)
      - Florence (Box 11)
        - Orsanmichele (Box 11)
        - Baptistry [Slide box 65] (Box 11)
          - North doors (Box 11)
          - East doors (Box 11)
            - Whole door (Box 11)
              - Details (Box 11)
                - Adam & Eve (Box 11)
                - Cain & Abel (Box 11)
                - David (Box 11)
                - Isaac (Box 11)
                - Jacob & Esau (Box 11)
                - Joseph (Box 11)
                - Joshua (Box 11)
                - Moses (Box 11)
                - Noah (Box 11)
                - Self-portrait [Slide box 66] (Box 11)
                - Solomon (Box 11)
    - Giorgetti, Antonio, d.1670 (Box 11)
    - Giovanni d'Ambrogio (Box 11)
    - Giovanni di Balducci, 1290-1350 (Box 11)
    - Giovanni da Bologna, 1524-1608 (Box 11)
      Xx Portrait drawing by Goltzius see Painting Holland
      - Bologna (Box 11)
      - Florence (Box 11)
        - Various Museums (Box 11)
        - Loggia dei Lanzi (Box 11)
        - Bargello (Box 11)
        - Piazza Annunziata (Box 11)
        - Piazza Signoria (Box 11)
      - Pratolino (Box 11)
      - Vienna [Slide boxes 66-67] (Box 11–12)
    - Giovanni da Firenze, ca.1343-1345 [Slide box 67] (Box 12)
    - Giovanni da Udine, 1487-1564 (Box 12)
    - Girolamo da Treviso, 1497-1544 (Box 12)
    - Giusti, Antonio & Giovanni (Box 12)
    - Giuliani, Giovanni, 1663-1744 (Box 12)
    - Greco, Emilio (Box 12)
    - Guelfi, Giovanni, ac.c.1714-34 (Box 12)
    - Guglielmo da Pisa, ca.1235-1311 (Box 12)
      X Guglielmo, Fra
    - Guidi, Domenico, 1625-1701 (Box 12)
    - Jacopo da Firenze (Box 12)
    - Kounellis, Jannis, 1936- (Box 12)
    - Lamberti, Niccolo di Piettro (Box 12)
    - Lamberti, Pietro (Box 12)
      X Lamberti, Pietro or Nanni di Bartolo
    - Landini, Taddeo, ca.1517-1594 (Box 12)
      Xx for Fountain of the Tortoises, Arch. Renaissance Italy, Rome Fountain
    - Lardera, Berto, 1911- (Box 12)
    - La Rocca, Ketty, 1938- (Box 12)
    - Laurana, Francesco, 1420-1502 [Slide boxes 67-68] (Box 12)
      - Vienna [Slide box 68] (Box 12)
      - Washington (Box 12)
    - Lautizio di Meo, 16th century (Box 12)
    - Leonardo da Vinci, 1452-1519 (Box 12)
    - Leoncillo, 1915-1968 (Box 12)
    - Leoni, Leone, 1509-1590 (Box 12)
    - Leoni, Pompeo, ca.1533-1608 (Box 12)
    - Leopardi, Alessandro (Box 12)
    - Lombardi, Lodovico, 1507-1575 (Box 12)
    - Lombardo, Antonio, ca.1458-1516 (Box 12)
    - Lombardo, Pietro, ca.1435-1515 (Box 12)
    - Lombardo, Tullio, ca.1455-1532 (Box 12)
    - Lorenzi, Battista, 1527-1594 (Box 12)
    - Lorenzi, Stoldo, 1534-1583 (Box 12)
    - Maderno, Stefano, 1576-1636 (Box 12)
    - Maitani, Lorenzo, 1275-1330 (Box 12)
      Xx for general views of Reliefs on Orvieto Cathedral- Arch. Gothic Italy- Orvieto Cathedral
    - Manno di Bandino, ac.1300-1312 [Slide box 69] (Box 12)
    - Mantegazza, Antonio, d.1495 (Box 12)
    - Manzoni, Piero, 1933-1963 (Box 12)
    - Manzu, Giacomo, 1908- (Box 12)
      - Doors (Box 12)
      - Figures (Box 12)
        - Cardinals (Box 12)
        - Dance Steps (Box 12)
        - David (Box 12)
        - Guantanamera (Box 12)
        - Young Girls (Box 12)
        - Women [Slide box 70] (Box 12)
      - Groups (Box 12)
        - Lovers (Box 12)
      - Heads (Box 12)
    - Maratti, Francesco, 1686-1719 (Box 12)
    - Mariani, Camillo, 1556-1611 (Box 12)
    - Marigliano, Giovanni, 1488-1558 (Box 12)
    - Marini, Marino, 1901- (Box 12)
      - Drawings (Box 12)
      - Dancers (Box 12)
      - Elements (Box 12)
      - Horses (Box 12)
      - Jugglers (Box 12)
      - Miracles (Box 12)
      - Pomona (Box 12)
      - Portrait Heads (Box 12)
        - Riders (Box 12)
        - Warriors (Box 12)
    - Martini, Arturo, 1889-1947 (Box 12)
    - Mascoli Master (Box 12)
    - Masegne, J & P., 1383-1409 [Slide box 71] (Box 12)
      X Masegne, Jacobello & Pierpaolo
    - Maso di Bartolommeo, 1406-1456 (Box 12)
    - Mauri, Fabio, 1926- (Box 12)
    - Mazzoni, Guido, 1450-1518 (Box 12)
      - Busseto (Box 12)
      - Ferrara (Box 12)
      - Modena (Box 12)
      - Naples (Box 12)
    - Mazzuoli, Giuseppe, 1644-1725 (Box 12)
    - Melotti, Fausto, 1901-1986 (Box 12)
    - Menghini, Niccolo, 1610-1655 (Box 12)
    - Mercia, Niccolo di Cecco Del, -1370 (Box 12)
    - Merz, Mario, 1925- (Box 12)
    - Michelangelo, 1475-1564 (Box 12)
      Xx for drawings & sketches of Medici Tombs –Painting Italy- Michelangelo, drawings-
      XX for drawings & sketches of Julius II Tomb –Painting Italy- Michelangelo, drawings-
      - General (Box 12)
      - Comparisons [Slide boxes 71-72] (Box 12)
      - Sculptures [Slide boxes 72] (Box 12)
        - Bologna (Box 12)
        - Bruges (Box 12)
        - Florence (Box 12)
          - Accademia (Box 12)
            - David (Box 12)
            - Pieta Palestrina (Box 12)
            - S. Matthew (Box 12)
            - Slaves (Box 12)
          - Bargello (Box 12)
            - Bacchus (Box 12)
            - Brutus (Box 12)
            - Madonna & Child (Pitti Madonna) [Slide box 73] (Box 13)
          - Casa Buonarroti (Box 13)
            - Battle of Centaurs (Box 13)
            - Madonna of the Stairs (Box 13)
          - Duomo (Box 13)
          - S. Lorenzo (Box 13)
            - Tomb of Giuliano (Box 13)
              - Day (Box 13)
              - Night (Box 13)
            - Tomb of Lorenzo (Box 13)
              - Dawn (Box 13)
              - Twilight (Box 13)
          - Pal. Vecchio [Slide box 74] (Box 13)
        - London (Box 13)
        - Milan (Box 13)
        - Paris (Box 13)
          Xx Rebelious slave for drawing by Cezanne –Painting France Cezanne-
        - Rome (Box 13)
          - S. Peter's (Box 13)
            - Pieta (Box 13)
          - S. Pietro in Vincoli (Box 13)
            - Moses (Box 13)
    - Michelozzo, (attributed to) 1396-1472 (Box 13)
      Xx for Outdoor Pulpit in Prato –Sculpture Italy- Donatello & Michelozzo
    - Minguzzi, Luciano, 1911- (Box 13)
    - Mino da Fiesole, 1430-1484 [Slide boxes 74-75] (Box 13)
    - Mirko, (Basadella), 1910- [Slide box 75] (Box 13)
    - Mochi, Francesco, 1580-1654 (Box 13)
    - Modigliani, Amadeo, 1884-1920 (Box 13)
    - Monaco, Guglielmo, -1489 (Box 13)
    - Monaldi, Carlo, 1683-1760 (Box 13)
    - Montelupo, Baccia da, 1469-1535 (Box 13)
    - Montelupo, Raffaello da, 1505-1566/7 (Box 13)
    - Montorsoli, G.A., 1507-1563 (Box 13)
    - Mosca, Giovanni Maria, 1515-1553 (Box 13)
    - Munari, Bruno, 1907- (Box 13)
    - Naccherino, Michelangelo, 1550-1622 (Box 13)
    - Nanni di Bartolo, 1419-1451 (Box 13)
      Xx for Annunciation panels, for Brenzoni Monument –Painting Italy- Pisanello- Verona, S. Ferma Magiore.
      Xx for Justice of Solomon from Doge's Palace, Venice see Lamberti, Pietro
    - Niccolo dell'Arca, 1463-1494 (Box 13)
    - Niccolo de Bartolommeo (Box 13)
    - Oderisi, Pietro, 1268-1299 (Box 13)
    - Orcagna, Andrea di Cione, 1308-1368 [Slide box 76] (Box 13)
    - Paladino, Mimmo, 1948- (Box 13)
    - Paolini, Giulio, 1940- (Box 13)
    - Pascali, Pino, 1935-1968 (Box 13)
    - Penone, Giusepe, 1947- (Box 13)
    - Persico, Paolo, 1729-1780 (Box 13)
    - Picano, Giuseppe (Box 13)
    - Pierino da Vinci, 1520-1554 (Box 13)
    - Piero di Giovanni Tedesco (Box 13)
    - Pila, Giacomo della, 1471-1502 (Box 13)
    - Pisano, Andrea, 1270-1349 (Box 13)
      - Florence (Box 13)
        - Baptistry (Box 13)
        - Campanile (Box 13)
        - Museo Del Duomo [Slide box 77] (Box 13)
    - Pisano, Giovanni, 1245-1314 (Box 13)
      - Pisa (Box 13)
      - Pistoia (Box 13)
      - Siena (Box 13)
    - Pisano, Niccolo, 1220-1278 (Box 13)
      Xx for detail of the Tomb of S. Domenic –Sculpture Italy- Michelangelo, Niccolo dell'Arca, Arnolfo di Cambio (Raising of Napoleon Orsini)
      Xx for Phaedra Sarcophagus -Sculpture Roman- Sarcophagal Mythological
      - Pisa (Box 13)
      - Siena (Box 13)
    - Pisano, Niccolo & Giovanni (Box 13)
    - Pisano, Nino, ca.1349-1368 (Box 13)
    - Pisano, Tommaso (Box 13)
    - Pistoletto, Michelangelo, 1933- (Box 13)
    - Pittoni, Girolamo, 15th century (Box 13)
    - Pizzolo, Niccolo, ca.141-1453 (Box 13)
    - Pollaiuolo, Antonio, 1432-1498 (Box 13)
      X Pollaiuolo, Antonio & Piero
    - Pomodoro, Arnaldo, 1926- (Box 13)
    - Ponzio, Flaminio (Box 13)
    - Porta, Guglielmo della, ca.1531-1557 (Box 13)
    - Prestinari, M.A. (Box 13)
    - Queirolo, Francesco, 1704-1762 (Box 13)
    - Quercia, Jacopo della, 1367-1438 (Box 13)
      X Della Quercia, Jacopo
      - Bologna [Slide box 79] (Box 14)
      - Lucca (Box 14)
      - Siena (Box 14)
      - Washington (Box 14)
    - Quercia, Piero D'Angelo Della (Box 14)
    - Raggi, Antonio, 1624-168 (Box 14)
      Xx Architecture Renaissance Italy- Rome, Il Gesu- S. Marcello al Corso
    - Raverti, Matteo (style of) (Box 14)
    - Ricciarelli, Daniele, 1509-1566 (Box 14)
      X Daniele da Volterra
    - Il Riccio (see Briosco) (Box 14)
    - Rizzo, Antonio, ca.1465-1499 (Box 14)
    - Robbia, Andrea della, 1435-1525 [Slide boxes 79-80] (Box 14)
    - Robbia, Giovanni della, 1469-1529 [Slide 80] (Box 14)
      X Della Robbia, Giovanni
    - Robbia, Girolamo della, 1488-1566 (Box 14)
    - Robbia, Luca della, 1400-1482 (Box 14)
      - Florence (Box 14)
        - Bargello (Box 14)
        - Campanille (Box 14)
        - Duomo (Box 14)
          - Cantoria (Box 14)
          - S. Croce (Box 14)
    - Roccatagliata, Niccolo, late 16th – early 17th century (Box 14)
    - Romano, Giovanni Christoforo, ca.1470-1512 (Box 14)
    - Rosselli, Domenico di G., ca. 1439-1497 (Box 14)
    - Rossellino, Antonio, 1427-1479 (Box 14)
    - Rossellino, Bernardo, 1407-1464 (Box 14)
    - Rossi, Angelo de, 1671-1720 (Box 14)
    - Rossi, Properzia de', 1491-1530 (Box 14)
    - Rossi, Vincenzo di, 1525-1587 (Box 14)
    - Rosso, Giovanni di Bartolo (Box 14)
    - Ross, Medardo, 1858-1928 (Box 14)
    - Rusconi, Camillo, 1658-1728 (Box 14)
    - Russolo, Luigi, 1885-1947 (Box 14)
    - Rustici, G.F., 1474-1554 (Box 14)
    - San Gallo, Francesco da, 1494-1576 (Box 14)
    - Sangallo, Giuliano da, 1445-1516 (Box 14)
    - Sanmartino, Giuseppe, 1720-1793 (Box 14)
    - Sansovino, Andrea, 1460-1529 [Slide boxes 81-82] (Box 14)
    - Sansovino, Jacopo, 1486-157[Slide boxes 82] (Box 14)
      - Washington (Box 14)
    - Santacrose, Girolamo da, ca.1502-1537 (Box 14)
    - Sant'Agata, Franceso da, ca.1520 (Box 14)
    - Scalza, Ippolito, ca.1532-1617 (Box 14)
    - Schiaffino, Francesco, 1689-1765 (Box 14)
    - Severo da Ravenna, ca.1500 (Box 14)
    - Silvestro De Sulmona, -1504 (Box 14)
    - Sirone, Mario, 1885-1961 (Box 14)
    - Slodtz, Michelangelo, 1705-1764 (Box 14)
    - Solari, Cristoforo, 1460-1527 (Box 14)
    - Solari, Pietro, ca.1481-1490 (Box 14)
    - Soldani, Massimiliano, 1656-1740 (Box 14)
    - Susine, Clemente, 1754-1805 (Box 14)
    - Tacca, Pietro, 1577-1640 (Box 14)
    - Tasso, Leonardo Del, 1466-1500 (Box 14)
    - Tino di Camaino, 1285-1337 (Box 14)
    - Torrigiano, Pietro, 1472-1528 (Box 14)
    - Tribolo, Niccolo, 1485-1550 (Box 14)
    - Turini, Giovanni, 1349-1438 (Box 14)
    - Valdambrino, Francesco [Slide box 83] (Box 14)
    - Vasari, Giorgio, 1511-1574 (Box 14)
    - Il Vecchietta, ca.1412-1480 (Box 14)
    - Verrocchio, Andrea Del, 1435-1488 (Box 14)
      - Berlin (Box 14)
      - Florence (Box 14)
        - Bargello (Box 14)
          - Various titles (Box 14)
          - David, 1470-1475 (Box 14)
        - Orsanmichele (Box 14)
        - Palazzo Pitti (Box 14)
        - Palazzo Vecchio (Box 14)
        - S. Lorenzo (Box 14)
      - New York (Box 14)
      - Venice (Box 14)
      - Washington (Box 14)
        - National Gallery (Box 14)
          - Guiliano De'Medici (Box 14)
          - Lorenzo De'Medic [Slide box 84] (Box 14)
        - Putto (Box 14)
    - Vittoria, Alessandro, 1525-1608 (Box 14)
    - Viva, Angelo, ac.1772-1816 (Box 14)
    - Zorio, Gilberto, 1944- (Box 14)
- Lebanon (Box 14)
  - Hatoum, Mona, 1952- (Box 14)
- Poland (Box 14)
  - Various Artists (Box 14)
- Rumania (Box 14)
  - Brancusi, Constantin, 1876-1957 (Box 14)
    - Various Titles (Box 14)
    - Artist's Studio (Box 14)
    - Bird (Box 14)
    - Blonde Negrees (Box 14)
    - Endless Column [Slide box 85] (Box 15)
    - Fish (Box 15)
    - Leda (Box 15)
    - Mademoiselle Pogany (Box 15)
    - Princess X (Box 15)
    - Sleeping Muse (Box 15)
    - Torso (Box 15)
    - New York (Box 15)
      - Guggenheim Museum (Box 15)
      - Museum of Modern Art (Box 15)
    - Paris (Box 15)
    - Philadelphia [Slide boxes 85-86] (Box 15)
    - Venice [Slide box 86] (Box 15)
  - Brauner, Victor, 1903-1966 (Box 15)
  - Janco, Marcel, 1895- (Box 15)
- Russia (Box 15)
  - Various Titles & Various Artists (Box 15)
  - Altmann, Nathan, 1889- (Box 15)
  - Archipenko, Alexander, 1887- (Box 15)
    Xx for Advertisement by Marcel Duchamp of Archipenko exhibit at Societe Anonyme Gallery, 1921 see Painting france- Marcel Duchamp.
  - Baranoff-Rossine, V., 1888-1942 (Box 15)
  - Exter, Alexandra, 1882-1949 (Box 15)
  - Gabo, Naum, 1890- (Box 15)
    - Various Titles (Box 15)
    - London (Box 15)
    - New Haven (Box 15)
    - New York [Slide box 87] (Box 15)
  - Gordine, Dora, 1906- (Box 15)
  - Kerbel, L. (Box 15)
  - Kobro, Katarzyna, 1898-1951 (Box 15)
  - Kremer, F. (Box 15)
  - Lebedev, Vladimir, 1891-1967 (Box 15)
  - Malevich, Kasmir, 1878-1935 (Box 15)
  - Mudenetsky, K.K., 1899-1936 (Box 15)
  - Mukhina, Vera, 1889-1953 (Box 15)
  - Pevsner, Antoine, 1886-1962 (Box 15)
  - Puni, Ivan, 1894-1956 (Box 15)
  - Rodchenko, Alexandre, 1891-1956 (Box 15)
    X Rodcenko, Aleksandr Mihailovi
  - Stenberg, Georgli, 1900-1933 (Box 15)
  - Stenberg, Vladimir, 1899- (Box 15)
  - Tatlin, Vladimir, E., 1885-1953 (Box 15)
    - Letatlin (Box 15)
    - Monument to 3rd International [Slide box 88] (Box 15)
  - Troubetzkoy, Paolo, 1866-1938 (Box 15)
    X Troubetzkoy, Prince Paolo
  - Zadkine, Ossip, 1890- (Box 15)
- Spain (Box 15)
  - Artist Unknown (Box 15)
  - 11th century (Box 15)
  - 12th century (Box 15)
  - 13th century (Box 15)
    - Gothic (Box 15)
  - 15th century (Box 15)
    - Renaissance [Slide boxes 88-89] (Box 15)
  - 16th century [Slide box 89] (Box 15)
  - 17th century (Box 15)
  - Known Artists (Box 15)
    - Avila, Juan (Box 15)
    - Balba, Jeronimo de, ac.1706-1750 (Box 15)
    - Berrocal, Miguel, 1933- (Box 15)
    - Berruguette, Alonso, 1480-1561 (Box 15)
      - Valladolid (Box 15)
        - Sculpture Museum (Box 15)
          - Various titles (Box 15)
          - La Mejorada Altar (Box 15)
          - S. Benito Altar (Box 15)
    - Bigarny, F. (Box 15)
    - Bonarelli, Matteo (Box 15)
    - Cano, Alonso, 1601-1667 [Slide boxes 89-90] (Box 15)
    - Carmona, Luis Salvador, 1730-1807 [Slide box 90] (Box 15)
    - Chillida, Eduardo, 1924- (Box 15)
    - Dali, Salvador, 1904- (Box 15)
    - Dominguez, Oscar, 1906-1957 (Box 15)
    - Duque Cornejo, Pedro, 1678-1757 (Box 15)
    - Fanelli & Revilla (Box 15)
      X Fanelli, V. & Revilla, Juan O.
    - Fernandez, Gregorio, 1576-1636 (Box 15)
    - Forment, Damian, d.1541 (Box 15)
    - Gargallo, Pablo, 1881-1934 (Box 15)
    - Gonzalez, Julio, 1876-1942 (Box 15)
    - Gonzalez, Manuel (Box 15)
    - Gris, Juan, 1887-1927 (Box 15)
    - Juni, Juan de, ca.1507-1577 [Slide boxes 90-91] (Box 15–16)
    - Leoni, Pompeo, ca.1533-1608 [Slide box 91] (Box 16)
    - Lopez, Francisco, 1932- (Box 16)
    - Lopez-Garcia, Antonio, 1936- (Box 16)
    - Mena, Pedro de, 1628-1688 (Box 16)
    - Miro, Joan, 1893-1983 (Box 16)
    - Montañes, Juan Martinez, 1568-1649 (Box 16)
    - Mora, Diego de (Box 16)
    - Mora, José de (Box 16)
    - Navarro, Miguel, 1945- (Box 16)
    - Ordoñez, Bartholomew, 1520 (Box 16)
    - Picasso, Pablo, 81-1973 (Box 16)
      Xx for comparisons with African sculptures see Sculpture Central Africa Ossyeba people (Gabon), Sculpture West Africa- Brebo people
      - 1900-1909 (Box 16)
      - 1910-1919 [Slide boxes 91-92] (Box 16)
      - 1920-1929 [Slide box 92] (Box 16)
      - 1930-1939 (Box 16)
      - 1940-1949 (Box 16)
      - 1950-1959 (Box 16)
      - 1960-1973 [Slide box 93] (Box 16)
    - Plensa, Jaume, 1955- (Box 16)
    - Rincon, F. (Box 16)
    - Risueno, Jose, 1665-1732 (Box 16)
    - Rodrigo de Leon (Box 16)
    - Rodan, Pedro, 1624-1699 (Box 16)
    - Ruiz, de Peral, Torcuato (Box 16)
    - Sanchez Perez, Alberto, 1895-1962 (Box 16)
    - Sierra, Pedro de (Box 16)
    - Siloe, Diego de, 1495-1563 (Box 16)
    - Siloe, Gil de (Box 16)
    - Torres-Garcia, Joaquin, 1895- (Box 16)
    - Valmaseda, J., 1490-? (Box 16)
    - Vigarni, Felipe, 1470-1543 (Box 16)
    - Villabrille y Ron (Box 16)
    - Vitullo, Sesotrio (Box 16)
    - Zarzillo, Francisco, 1707-1781 (Box 16)
- Sweden (Box 16)
  - Various Artists (Box 16)
  - Milles, Carl, 1875-1955 (Box 16)
  - Sergel, Johan Tobias, 1740-1814 (Box 16)
- Switzerland (Box 16)
  - Artist Unknown (Box 16)
  - Armleder, John (Box 16)
  - Bill, Max, 1908- (Box 16)
  - Fischli & Weiss (Box 16)
  - Gerstner, Karl (Box 16)
  - Giacometti, Alberto, 1901-1965 (Box 16)
    Xx for Man Ray photograph of Palais de quatre Heures see Potography U.S. Man Ray
    - Before 1929 (Box 16)
    - 1930-1931 [Slide boxes 93-94] (Box 16)
    - 1932 [Slide box 94] (Box 16)
    - 1933-1939 (Box 16)
    - 1940-1949 (Box 16)
    - 1950-1959 (Box 16)
    - 1960-1969 (Box 16)
  - Klee, Paul, 1879-1940 (Box 16)
  - Oppenheim, Meret, 1913- (Box 16)
  - Panamerenko (Box 16)
  - Raetz, Markus, 1941- (Box 16)
  - Reutersward, Carl F., 1934- (Box 16)
  - Rist, Pipilotti, 1962- (Box 16)
  - Seligmann, Kurt, 1900-1962 (Box 16)
  - Spoerri, Daniel Isaac, 1930- (Box 16)
  - Taeuber-Arp, Sophie, 1889-1943 [Slide boxes 94-95] (Box 16)
  - Tinguely, Jean, 1925- [Slide box 95] (Box 16)
    - Before 1959 (Box 16)
    - 1960-1969 (Box 16)
- Yugoslavia (Box 16)
  - Various Artists (Box 16)
  - Mestrovic, Ivan, 1883 (Box 16)
- Latin America (Box 16)
  - Argentina (Box 16)
    - Various Artists (Box 16)
  - Bolivia (Box 16)
    - Various Artists (Box 16)
  - Brazil (Box 16)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 16)
    - Camargo, Sergio de, 1930- (Box 16)
    - Cemin, Saint Clair (Box 16)
    - Clark, Lygia, 1921- (Box 16)
    - G.T.O (Box 16)
    - Lisboa, Antonio Francisco [Slide box 96] (Box 16)
    - Louco, 1932- (Box 16)
    - Oiticica, Helio, 1937-1980 (Box 16)
    - Pereira Rego, Ronaldo, 1935- (Box 16)
    - Santos, Agnaldo dos, 1926-1962 (Box 16)
  - Chile (Box 16)
    - Various Artists (Box 16)
    - Vicuña, Cecilia, 1948- (Box 16)
  - Colombia (Box 16)
    - Various Artists (Box 16)
  - Cuba (Box 16)
    - Various Artists (Box 16)
    - Mendieta, Ana, 1948-1985 (Box 16)
  - Ecuador (Box 16)
    - Various Artists (Box 16)
  - Guatemala (Box 16)
    - Various Artists (Box 16)
  - Haiti [Slide box 97] (Box 17)
    - Vilaire, Patrick, 1941- (Box 17)
    - Liautaud, Georges (Box 17)
  - Jamaica (Box 17)
    - Various Artists (Box 17)
  - Honduras (Box 17)
    - Artist Unknown (Box 17)
  - Mexico (Box 17)
    - 16th century (Box 17)
    - 17th century (Box 17)
    - 18th century (Box 17)
    - 20th century (Box 17)
      - Artist Unknown (Box 17)
      - Artists known (Box 17)
      - Gómez-Peña, Guillermo, 1955- (Box 17)
      - Linares, Felipe, 1936- (Box 17)
      - Meireles, Cildo, 1943- (Box 17)
      - Orozco, Gabriel, 1952-[Slide box 98] (Box 17)
      - Tolsa, Manuel, 1757-1816 (Box 17)
  - Panama (Box 17)
    - General (Box 17)
  - Peru (Box 17)
    - Artists unknown & Popular Art (Box 17)
  - Venezuela (Box 17)
    - Various Artists (Box 17)
- United States (Box 17)
  - Group Material (Box 17)
  - Southwest (Box 17)
  - Artists Unknown (Box 17)
  - 17th century (Box 17)
  - 18th century (Box 17)
  - 19th century (Box 17)
    - Artist Unknown [Slide boxes 98-99] (Box 17)
    - Animals, General (not weathervanes) [Slide boxes 99] (Box 17)
    - Figure heads (Box 17)
    - Weathervanes (Box 17)
  - 20th century (Box 17)
    - Various titles (Box 17)
    - Chicano Artists (Box 17)
    - Exhibitions (Box 17)
  - Artists Known (Box 17)
    - Various Artists (Box 17)
    - Aballea, Martine, 1950- (Box 17)
    - Acconci, Vitto, 1940- [Slide boxes 99-100] (Box 17)
    - Acker, Kathy, 1948-1997 [Slide box 100] (Box 17)
    - Adams, Alice, 1930- (Box 17)
    - Adams, Dennis (Box 17)
    - Adams, Mac, 1943- (Box 17)
    - Africano, Nicholas, 1948- (Box 17)
    - Agee, Ann, 1959- (Box 17)
    - Agostino, Peter (Box 17)
    - Ahearn, John, 1951- (Box 17)
    - Aitken, Doug, 1968- (Box 17)
    - Akers, Bejamin Paul, 1825-1861 (Box 17)
    - Albert, Calvin, 1918- (Box 17)
    - Albrizio, Humbert, 1901- (Box 17)
    - Ames, Alexander (Box 17)
    - Amino, Leo, 1911- (Box 17)
    - Anderson, Jeremy, 1921- (Box 17)
    - Anderson, John, 1928- (Box 17)
    - Ames, Asa, 1824-1851 (Box 17)
    - Anderson, Laurie, 1947- [Slide boxes 100-101] (Box 17)
    - Andre, Carl, 1935- [Slide box 101] (Box 17)
      - Various titles (Box 17)
      - Before 1966 (Box 17)
      - 1966-1969 (Box 17)
      - 1970- (Box 17)
    - Ant Farm (Box 17)
    - Antin, Eleanor, 1935- (Box 17)
    - Antonakos, Sthephen, 1926- (Box 17)
    - Antoni, Jamine, 1964- (Box 17)
    - Applebrook, Ida, 1929 (Box 17)
    - Armajanio,Siah, 1939- [Slide boxes 101-102] (Box 17)
      X Armajani,, Siah & Scott Burton
    - Arneson, Robert, 1930- [Slide box 102] (Box 17)
    - Arnold, Anne, 1925- (Box 17)
    - Artis, William, 1919- (Box 17)
    - Artschwager, Richard, 1924- (Box 17)
    - Asawa, Ruth [Slide box 103] (Box 18)
    - Asher, Michael, 1943- (Box 18)
    - Augur, Hezekiah, 1791-1858 (Box 18)
    - Aycock, Alice (Box 18)
      - -1976 (Box 18)
      - 1977 (Box 18)
      - 1978 (Box 18)
      - 1979- (Box 18)
      - Game of Fliers (Box 18)
    - Baizerman, Saul, 1889-1957 (Box 18)
    - Baker, Aaron, 1972- (Box 18)
    - Ball, Thomas, 1819-1911 (Box 18)
    - Barnard, George Grey, 1863-1938 (Box 18)
    - Barney, Matthew, 1967- (Box 18)
      - Various titles [Slide boxes 103-104] (Box 18)
      - Jim Otto Suite, 1990 [Slide box 104] (Box 18)
      - OTTOshaft, 1992 (Box 18)
      - Drawing Restrain 7, 1993 (Box 18)
      - Cremaster I, 1995 (Box 18)
      - Cremaster 4, 1994 (Box 18)
      - Cremaster 5, 1997 (Box 18)
    - Barron, Harris (Box 18)
    - Barry, Judith, 1949- (Box 18)
    - Barthe, Richmond, 1901-1989 (Box 18)
    - Bartholomew, Edward S., 1822-1858 (Box 18)
    - Bartlett, Paul W., 1865-1925 (Box 18)
    - Baskin, Leonard, 1922- (Box 18)
    - Baug, Thomas (Box 18)
    - Baur, Theodor, 1835-? (Box 18)
    - Beecroft, Vanessa, 1969- (Box 18)
    - Bell, Larry Stuart, 1939- (Box 18)
    - Benglis, Lynda, 1941- [Slide box 105] (Box 18)
    - Ben-Schmuel, Aaron, 1903- (Box 18)
    - Benton, Fletcher (Box 18)
    - Berkley, Sheila (Box 18)
    - Berman, Wallace, 1926- (Box 18)
    - Bertoia, Harry, 1915- (Box 18)
    - Bickerton, Ashley, 1950- (Box 18)
    - Bidlo, Mike (Box 18)
    - Biederman, Charles, 1906- (Box 18)
    - Biederman, James (Box 18)
    - Birnbaum, Dara, 1946- (Box 18)
    - Bladen, Larry, 1918- (Box 18)
    - Bladen, Ronald, 1918-1988 (Box 18)
    - Blake, Nayland, 1960- (Box 18)
    - Bloom, Barbara (Box 18)
    - Blondel, Michele (Box 18)
    - Blum, Andrea (Box 18)
    - Blythe, David G., 1815-1865 (Box 18)
    - Bochner, Mel, 1940- (Box 18)
    - Boghasian, Varujan, 1926- [Slide box 106] (Box 18)
    - Bohner, Thom (Box 18)
    - Bollinger, William (Box 18)
    - Bonnell, Mary (Box 18)
    - Bontecou, Lee, 1931- (Box 18)
    - Borglum, Glutzon, 1867-1941 (Box 18)
    - Borofsky, Jonathan, 1942- (Box 18)